<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NextGen</string>
    <string name="home_label">Home</string>
    <string name="nearby_label">Near By</string>
    <string name="notification_label">Notification</string>
    <string name="profile_label">Profile</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="nextgen">neXtGen</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">At NextGen, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our users. This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect, use, and safeguard your personal information when you use our mobile application - NextGen. By using our App, you consent to the practices described in this policy.\n\nWe collect personal information to provide and improve the services offered by the App. This information may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, phone number, and any other details you voluntarily provide when registering or using the App’s features. Additionally, we may collect certain non-personal information automatically, such as your device\'s unique identifiers, IP address, operating system, browser type, and usage patterns. This data is essential for optimizing the functionality of the App and enhancing your user experience.\n\nThe information collected is used to deliver the services you have requested, personalize your experience, and improve the App’s overall performance. For example, your personal information allows us to authenticate your identity, manage your account, and communicate with you about updates, promotions, or any changes to our terms of service. Non-personal information is typically used for diagnostic purposes, to analyze app usage trends, and to prevent fraud or security issues.\n\nWe take reasonable precautions to ensure the security of your personal data. We implement industry-standard measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, loss, misuse, or alteration. However, while we strive to keep your data secure, no system or electronic transmission is completely infallible, and therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security.\n\nWe do not share or sell your personal information to third parties, except as necessary to provide the services or as required by law. In certain circumstances, we may share your data with trusted third-party service providers who perform essential functions on our behalf, such as payment processing, hosting services, or data analytics. These third parties are bound by confidentiality agreements and are only permitted to use your data as necessary to perform their duties.\n\nFrom time to time, the App may contain links to third-party websites or services that are not operated by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies before sharing any personal information, as their policies may differ from ours.\n\nWe may update this Privacy Policy periodically to reflect changes in our practices or for other operational, legal, or regulatory reasons. When we make changes, we will notify you by updating the \"Effective Date\" at the top of this page. We encourage you to review this policy regularly to stay informed about how we protect your information.\n\nBy continuing to use the App after any changes to this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge and agree to the updated terms. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at [Insert Contact Information].</string>


</resources>